exclusivelyweddings.com 2017-11-07

# Privacy Policy | Terms and Conditions | ExclusivelyWeddings.com

### Effective: 11/2/2017

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.exclusivelyweddings.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by and for the use of Exclusively Weddings.

We may from time to time contract with third party vendors to provide ads to our customers on our behalf via the Internet or to send direct mail or catalogs to customers whom we think may be interested in our products or services. In order to do so, such vendor may collect anonymous information about your visits to our website using a 'cookie'. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser or mobile device by websites, mobile apps, and advertisements that you access or use. This data is stored on your browser or mobile device and helps website and mobile apps to remember things about you to improve your experience with the website. Third-party vendors may then pool the anonymous information that they collect from our website with other sources of information, which may include your name and mailing address, for purposes of determining whether you might be interested in receiving direct mail or a catalog. If you do not wish for cookies to be placed on your computer, most web browsers permit you to prevent that from taking place. However, please keep in mind that these technologies are an important part of how the website works; removing, rejecting or limiting the use of cookies or other similar technologies might affect the availability and functionality of the website. To opt-out of receiving our direct mail or catalogs, you may send us an email at service@exclusivelyweddings.com or call us at 1.800.759.7666.

**Terms and Conditions**   
Important Note: Descriptive, typographic, photographic or computer-generated errors are unintended and subject to correction. We cannot be liable for incorrect photos, typographical errors or discontinued merchandise. 

**Our Commitment To Privacy**   
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

**The Information We Collect:**   
This notice applies to all information collected via the www.exclusivelyweddings.com website. Our Web site uses an online order form to make it easy for our customers to order our products or to request a copy of our print catalog. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: 

_Contact Address_ : This is your permanent mailing address. We need this information in case we cannot get in touch with you by phone or email and need to ask you important information regarding your order.

_Shipping Address_ : This is where you want your order shipped. Ideally, this is an address where someone will be available to receive your package. If you want us to ship to your office, be sure to give us the name of the company and suite or floor number to make sure that the delivery company can find you.

_Billing Address_ : This is the address where your credit card bill is sent. In order to make sure that an unauthorized person is not using your credit card, we subscribe to Address Verification through our credit card processor. They will verify that the Billing Address you give us matches the address where your credit card bill is sent. If there is not a match, we will contact you for further information. We have provided a convenient box to check if these addresses are the same as your Contact Address.

_Telephone Number and E-mail Address_ : This information is needed in case we have a question regarding your order.

_Wedding Date_ : This will ensure that we get your order to you before your wedding date.

**The Way We Use Information:**   
We use the information you provide when placing an order to complete the fulfillment, payment and delivery of that order. 

We use non-identifying and aggregate information, such as the internet domain address, about your visit to our site to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals from a particular geography visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form. 

Information sharing can provide a valuable type of consumer networking. By helping to make new connections and introduce new resources to our customers, you may discover new opportunities and products compatible with your interests and needs. With that end in mind, some customer information is shared with other select companies whose products and services you may find useful. Please note that sensitive information, such as credit card data, is never shared.

We appreciate and respect that not all customers may wish to benefit from the opportunity to share information with other select companies. If you do not want Exclusively Weddings to share your customer information, please immediately contact us and we will remove your name from lists we share with other companies. After the six to eight week time period it takes to process your request, your information will no longer be shared. When contacting us, please clearly state your request, including your name, mailing address, email address, and phone number.

**Our Commitment To Data Security:**   
We have a firm commitment to ensuring that others do not intercept the private information that you provide to us. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

At any point where we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data) the information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way, using the industry best practice of Secure Session Certification. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.

If at any time you don't see the address starting with https while on the checkout pages, please [email us](http://www.exclusivelyweddings.com/email-us.html) to alert us of this immediately.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who are authorized to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept and maintained in a secure environment. 

Instructions for updating your browser to a current version are available [here](http://browser-update.org/update.html). 

**Feedback**   
Your feedback is important to us. To help us improve our privacy policy and practice, you may [email us](http://www.exclusivelyweddings.com/email-us.html) or call us at **1.800.759.7666**.
